<helpDefinition>
  <title>Repo Help</title>
  <componentContainer>
<LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/ECSCM-Repo/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
<div class="help" >
    <h1 class="help">Repo</h1>
        <h2 class="help">Overview</h2>
        <p class="help">
            The ECSCM-Repo plugin allows ElectricCommander to communicate with your Repo, to download Git repositories. This plugin enables you to perform code checkout, preflight actions, and continuous integration.
        </p>
        <p class="help">
            <b>Note:</b> Repo must be installed and must be accessible from the command line.
            </p>
    
        <p class="help">
                    <b>Supported tool version</b><br/>
                    This plugin was developed and tested with Repo version 1.7.4.3.
                </p>
    
            <h2 class="help">Configuration</h2>
              <p class="help">
              To enable Commander to communicate with Repo, create a Source Control configuration, supplying the following information:
             </p>
             <ul>
				<li><b>Configuration Name</b> - Provide a unique name for the configuration, keeping in mind that you may need to create additional configurations over time.</li>
                <li><b>Description</b> - You can supply a text description for your reference only. Commander does not use this information.</li>
                <li><b>Manifest repository URL</b> - The url from which to retrieve a manifest repository. For the Android project it is git://android.git.kernel.org/platform/manifest.git</li>
				<li><b>Manifest</b> - The manifest file within the repository defined in the previous field. If no manifest name is selected, the default is default.xml</li>
				<li><b>Mirror the repositories</b> - Select this option to create a local mirror of the repositories. </li>
            </ul>
            
    
        <h2 class="help">Using the Plugin</h2>
        <p class="help">
                    See the <a href="/commander/link/showHelp?page=plugins&amp;section=using">Commander online help system</a> for details about how to use this plugin within a procedure.
                    </p>
                    <p class="help">
                    When you provide information for this plugin, fill-in the fields as follows:
                 </p>
    
            <h3 class="help">Source Control Management Checkout</h3>
            <ul>
                    <li><b>dest</b> - Indicate the path relative to the job's workspace where the source tree will be created.</li>
                    <li><b>RepoAgentPath</b> - Select this option if you created a property called "repo_working_dir" in the resource to avoid downloading the entire repository each time.</li>
                    <li><b>RepoProjectList</b> - Specify a list of projects to be downloaded.</li>
                    <li><b>RepoBranch</b> - Specify the git branch to fetch from repo.</li>
            </ul>
        <p></p>
        
        <h3 class="help">Source Control Management Preflight</h3>
            <ul>
                    <li><b>repoworkdir</b> - Supply the path to the developer working directory.</li>
                    <li><b>agentworkdir</b> - Supply the path to the source directory used by the agent.</li>
                    <li><b>RepoBranch</b> - Specify the git branch to fetch from repo.</li>
            </ul>
        <p></p>
        
        <h3 class="help">Source Control Management Sentry</h3>
            <ul>                    
                    <li><b>RepoAgentPath</b> - Select this option if you created a property called "repo_working_dir" in the resource to avoid downloading the entire repository each time.</li>
                    <li><b>RepoBranch</b> - Indicate the git branch to watch.</li>
            </ul>
        <p></p>
    
        <h2 class="help">Additional Information</h2>
        <p class="help">
        </p><ul>
                <li> <a href="http://source.android.com/source/using-repo.html">Repo Technical Documentation</a> </li>
            </ul>
        <p></p>
    
        <h2 class="help">Release Notes</h2>
        <p></p><h3 class="help">ECSCM-Repo 1.0.0</h3>
        <ul>
             <li>SCM features - Sentry </li>
             <li>SCM features - Checkout </li>
            <li>SCM features - Preflight </li>
		</ul>
</div>
</componentContainer>
</helpDefinition>